[Music]
Hey guys, you know liquidity sweeps
happen every single day, but not every
liquidity sweep is tradable, right? So,
in this video, I will show you how I
confirm liquidity sweep and decide if
it's hyper probability or just drop. And
hey, if this helps you out, don't forget
to hit the like button and subscribe. It
really supports the channel. Well, guys,
when we see the picture like this, we
got liquidity sip price trying to expect
for a value gap. Just tell me if this
information is enough to say yeah I can
short from here that's high probability
short or normally you're waiting for
more confirmation. Personally guys when
I see price is expecting height to frame
for a volume gap and offer sweep. This
information is not enough for me yet to
immediately enter the trade when I see
yeah we just swep this high. Let's just
short this. Obviously it's not what I
want to see. I would like to get more
confirmation to get better entry. Okay
guys, first I would like to start with
high frame level that I use. I don't use
all PDAs available in this world. I use
only fair value gaps, order blocks and I
use old liquidity levels. But I'm not
going to jump between time frames like
one minute chart, two minute chart,
three minute chart or maybe daily chart
to find this fair value gaps, order
blocks or old liquidity levels. No,
personally I use only 15 minute fair
value gap order block or old liquidity
level, 30 minute and hourly. That's
information will be enough for me to
build intraday bias and frame my trade.
Maybe right now it's going to sound
wild. But even if price is expected 15
minute for a value gap or 15 minute or
30 minute order block, I will still use
only two potential sweeps to confirm
reaction from this PD race. It's going
to be either hourly potential sweep or
30 minute potential sweep. This means
let's say price is expecting 15 minute
fair value gap right now bish volume gap
in order to enter the trade I will
switch on 30 minute chart and I will see
if we got any potential 30 minute maybe
hourly sweeps as reaction from this
15inut fair value gap and yeah guys as I
said before let's say we expected for a
volume gap obviously I'm not going to
short every single sweep right no we
have potential 30 minute sweep as
reaction from this 15-minut for a value
gap I'm going to switch on three minute
chart and I would like to find if we got
order block once we got potential 30
minute SE but let's say we have nothing
on 30 minute chart we have hourly
potential SE I'm going to switch on five
minute chart and once you got this
potential sweep on hourly I would like
to find 5 minute order block as
confirmation of this sweep personally
guys I trade this setup on gold and
silver sometimes on ES but I would say
it works everywhere but key time that I
trades on gold or silver, sometimes on
oil. CL is going to be between 7 and
9:00 a.m. It's pre-market trade.
Sometimes we are going to get
hyperbility stop doing silver bullet. So
basically between 10 and 11, but I would
say most of the time set up will start
forming around like 9:50 a.m. New York
time. And yes, we we have nothing during
PM session. So it's just consolidation,
no volume, just slow. I don't trade PM
session on gold at all. But I do trade
this during Asia session. So best time
to trade during Asia kill zone or
session is going to be between 700 p.m.
and 1000 p.m. New York time. Well guys
as I have already said we must trade
potential sweep as reaction from 15
minute 30 minute or hourly P rate in the
direction of high frame trend. What do I
mean by this? If market is bullish,
extremely bullish on high time frame and
yeah we see price expecting 15 minute
for a value gap bearish for a value gap
obviously we want to be careful with
this because trend is bullish we
expecting beish yeah we may get scalp
but probably it's not going to be high
probability trade so the first point we
want to trade in the direction of high
time frame trend high frame bias after
this yes we want to see okay we're
bullish let's see if price expected 15
minute 30 minute or hourly PDA
preferably bullish PDAs and after this
as a reaction from this bullish PD race
for volume gap order block old liquidity
level we need to get potential hourly or
30 minutes of course you can use 15
minute potential sweep but at this point
you will use one minute chart to confirm
this of course you can use for chart as
potential sweep and 15-inut chart is
going to confirm the sweep but
personally consider intraday bias
consider that I don't want to have like
huge stop loss. I prefer to stick just
to 30-inut chart and hourly chart
because it gives me a better entry. Well
guys, we already to talk about if we
have potential hour or 30 minute SIP as
well as we talk about yeah we have a
potential hourly sweep. I'm going to
switch on five minute chart and see if
we got order block to confirm this
hourly SE. Same for 30 minute chart. If
we have potential 30 minute SE I would
like to switch on three minute chart and
see yeah do we have right now three
minute order blocks that confirm the SE
or not. So, and preferably consider the
time once again high probability setup
is going to between 7 and 9:00 a.m. New
York time. I am silver bullet and 7 to
10 p.m. New York time. Also guys, I
would like to share a tip with you. For
example, when we have potential hour or
30 minute sweep and we see we have
double or triple sweep. So, what do I
mean by this? So let's say we see we
have one candle swept two or three
previous highs or lows. For example, we
got one sweep, we got two sweeps with
one single candle. I call this double
sip. So basically it give us strong
confirmation of reversal retracement. So
it can be just another I would say
textbook A+ confirmation that yeah
probably we write with our bias probably
right with our trade and our sweep. So
it can be good confirmation once again
that yeah this zip is going to be high
probability. Well guys here is example
as you can see with one single candle we
have this low and we swep this low. So
we have double sweep. So here's real
example from hourly chart on gold from
last week we got one sweep we got two
sweep. So we got double sweep. Sometimes
we are going to get triple sweep. So
this means with one single candle we are
going to sweep three lows right or
highs. So what happens right after this
we got strong reversal. So once again it
doesn't mean like it always is going to
reverse from double or triple sleep. No
if we see we hit higher from level. If
you see yes you got reaction from this
higher from level on 30 minute or hourly
chart. So reaction is going to be
potential sweep this means yes double
can confirm strong high probability
setup over here. So basically if you
have let's say that's hourly chart we
got double zip with trying to respect
either 15 minute 30 minute or hourly PD
this means yes I'm going to switch on
five minute chart and I will try to find
OB and to confirm the sweep. So if I can
find OB I'm going to trade uh long and I
will feel more calm uh no stress because
I see we got lots of confirmation
especially this double sweep. So this
trade most likely will go in my favor.
Well guys, let's take a look at this
example. So that's our chart in gold. We
got one sweep. We got two sweep. So once
again, we are not going to look only for
double or triple zip. So here is the
case. We got double seep. So what we can
see? Uhhuh. Height from bias beish. We
want to trade in direction of height
from trend. It's beish. We hit higher
from level. Once again it can be old
liquidity. So can I validate it as
higher from level? Yeah, it's old
liquidity level. Of course, it can be
higher from frame level, higher frame
ped, but also we can check 30 minute
chart. Maybe we have OB for value gap or
on 15inut chart. Yeah. So, we have two
two uh points over here. High frame
level. Perfect. Amazing. And height of
frame bias. Perfect. Amazing. So, next
question. Do we have potential hourly or
30 minutes as reaction from this high
frame level? Yeah, we do have it. So,
once your tree is done, so next
question. So once you got at this point
potential hourly sweep, I need to switch
on five minute chart and make sure if I
have OB if I have OB on five minute
chart. So yes, we have confirmation of
potential sweep. But maybe we have
something on 30-inut chart. Let's say uh
with this hourly potential sweep, we
also have 30 minute sweep. So the most
common question, let's say I have hourly
and 30 minute SE at the same time. So
I'm going to use 20 minute zip and three
minute OB because it's going to give me
better entry with better stop loss. As
we can see I switch on five minute
chart. Yes, here is a double sweep. And
yes, 5 minute order block confirmed.
Next question. Are we inside this time
window between 7 and 9:00 a.m.? Maybe
silver bullet. I am silver bullet. Maybe
Asia session between 7:10 p.m. Or maybe
it's just PM session. Yeah, we're
trading between 10 and 11. It's right. I
am silver bullet. So perfect. All rules
met. So what do you want to do? Just
trade this. But where should I execute?
Where is my entry? Where I need to put
my stop loss? Where is my TP for this
model? So entry is going to be once you
got order block. So basically I'm going
to use sequence of up or down close
candles. You can just use one single
candle. I have video about this how to
pick right OB. But I personally prefer
to use sequence of up close candles. And
I'm going to include like entire candle
if we have small wick but we got bigger
wick over here. I'm going to use body.
So we got the closure below sequence of
up close candles over here. So I'm going
to place my trade at the open of next
candle. I'm going to put my stop loss
always at swing high or swing low. So at
this point I'm going to put my stop loss
at swing high and I'm going to aim for 2
R. So here's a point once again. I'm not
going to measure two R from my actual
entry. So let's say I enter it at this
level, not at the open of next candle,
right? Somewhere here. So this means I'm
not going to measure 2 R from my entry.
I need to measure 2 R from the entry
where I had to enter. If you enter it
over here, okay, you are not going to
get two R with this trade. A bit less,
but it's okay. Just want to let you know
preferably to measure from open of next
candle. Stop loss swing high. my target
you are. Okay, let's say I miss a trade.
This happens happens a lot pretty often.
Or let's say I want to add to my trade.
I already enter it with small size. I
want to add a bit more. So it's okay for
my risk management. That's perfect.
Okay, we have option. So let's say we
miss this entry. We got perfect
potential hourly sip. This early sip was
confirmed by five minute order block.
One, two, three sequence of done close
candles. Entry at the open of next
candle. stop loss below swallow to RSTP.
But let's say I didn't see this. I miss
this. So another option, we need to wait
for new hourly or 30 minute candle. It
depends where was set up. If it was area
setup before 5 minute OB, you are going
to wait for candle and then use fresh
lower time frame order block created by
that new candle. Okay, let's say we got
sweep over here. It was confirmed by 5
minute OB. So I'm not going to touch any
other order blocks within this candle
anymore. I'm going to wait for new
hourly candle. And right after this
candle was opened, I'm going to wait for
new order block within this candle once
again. So let's say it was at 8:00 a.m.
we got new hourly candle, right? So I'm
going to wait for 5 minute OB after 8:00
a.m. not before. So as you can see, we
got 5 minute OB after 8:00 a.m. after
this hourly candle opened. I'm going to
put my entry as open of next candle with
stop loss below swing close which was
over here. I'm going to aim for two R or
I'm going to just leave this trade per
two R where it has to be over here. So
let's say it was 2 R here. I'm going to
just get probably five R at my another
entry or I can just close somewhere here
which is 2 R. It's up to you. So at this
point it was London high. I traded this
setup and it was last week. Well guys, I
already talked about the time but I'm
going to repeat this again. I trade this
on gold, silver and oil. And once again,
it works on ES, it works on ENQ, it
works on any other markets, but
personally, it works better on these
three instruments for me. So, as I said,
best time is going to be premarket, I am
silver bullet, and Asia session. So, it
doesn't really work during PM session
simply because we inside the chop. And I
noticed when I enter this trade, this
kind of trade, yes, we got reaction from
higher from level $15 block. Yes, you
got potential Cas confirmation. But
let's say it's PM session. And if I see
uh once I enter the trade, it's chop
chop chop just consolidation. I'm going
to cut this trade because I know how it
works, but this model should go
immediately in your favor. I know it
sounds wild, but model preferably, not
preferably, almost always goes
immediately in your favor. you can be in
draw down a little bit but if you see
once you enter it it's just
consolidating like doesn't really want
to move I prefer to cut this trade uh
because according to my observations
most of the time once it starts in
consolidating probably it's going to be
loss so I know how it works but it's
great in validation if you see price
just once you enter 30 minute 20 minute
inside consolidation just cut this trade
so on sometimes it's going to be with an
hour like perfect times like pre-market
ambul an Asia session. But when you see
if you're trying to trade during PM
session, which is I don't recommend at
all, you see just consolidation after
you enter the trade, just cut this
trade. Most likely, it just going to
stop you out or you're going to see it
until the end of the day. But once
again, even if it's like perfect time to
trade and you see it doesn't want to go
in your favor, maybe not immediately,
but after 5 minutes you enter it, I
would cut this trade. So I consider this
a low probability trade if it's just
consolidating for more than 5 minutes
after we enter the trade. Lots of people
ask me what has been rate for this
strategy. So let's try to figure this
out. So I created back test session. So
we are going to book test and see what
is actually been rate for this strategy.
So so far I book tested 24 trades uh
with two R. So basically this reward is
two R and I got 79% win rate. So
basically I got five losses and 19
winning trades. So let's try to figure
this out and see how it goes. Well guys,
I finished my back testing. Uh it was
Tuesday, March 19, I got trades. So I'm
not going to jump any other weeks. I'm
going to just switch to Wednesday, March
20th. And let's see if you're going to
get winning trade or losing trade. Well
guys, here is a March 20th Wednesday. Uh
I open at 7:00 a.m. because best setups
starts from 7 to 9:00 a.m. 9:50 to 11:00
a.m. and 7:00 p.m. to 10 p.m. Uh so so
first we are going to see if we have
high frame levels such as 15 minute
order block, fair value gap uh 30 minute
or hourly. So so far what we can see we
have fair value gap higher
over here, right? the nearest liquidity
level probably is going to be over here.
So, and we have immediately balance. So,
basically we don't have for a while gap
here. This leg is balanced. So, on
hourly uh I cannot see uh any setups
just yet. So, once again setup yeah we
have potential SE on hourly but no we
are going to look for setup after 7 a.m.
We are going to wait for new sweep
somewhere here. We're going to find out
if we have something on 15-minut chart
to long to this for a value gap.
Otherwise, you will drop to sell side
liquidity first, I think, and then we
will see if it's going to offer another
reaction. So, as you can see, uh it's
only 7:00 a.m. We expected nothing yet.
And I would say I would try to play long
after taking liquidity here
because there's no levels here to
respect, right? I'm going to teach you
three minute chart first.
If it's going to drop like a lot at
least to take low at 2153.8
eight I will try to long to hourly for a
volume gap otherwise I will just short
to this liquidity level and I will see
if it's going to present opportunity for
long
nothing yet didn't take anything yeah
guys can you see this potential sweep
from nowhere even if it's going to play
out it's not what I want to take let's
see so what I see so far we have sweep
over here yeah we have double sweep
right but what is the issue um
it's from nowhere. We didn't expect any
level. So yeah, it's great confirmation
for the tracement. All right.
Same uh happens right now over here. As
you can see, we got triple sweep. One,
two, three. Let's see. Probably we have
nothing right now to trade for uh to
trade for short.
Uh no, I'm lying. We have uh for a
volume gap on 15 minute chart. Yeah, you
know guys, I'm going to probably short
this right now to this uh sell side or 2
hour uh at least in 15 for a volume gap,
right? So, and this for action for
volume gap confirmed by triple sweep on
30 minute chart. Let's see if we got
order block.
So, yes, we have OB. I will try to place
short right now.
So basically from the open of this
candle I'm going to put my stop loss at
swing high and I'm going to aim for two
R. Look at this guys. Two R at sell
side. Okay just one contract. So it's
one mini contract seems like. I'm going
to place a trade. I'm going to put my
stop at this Vai once again. I'm going
to aim for sell side.
Okay.
Let's see if it's going to go in my
favor. It stopped me out.
As you can see, still trying to for gap.
We have another potential sweep.
Uh, okay. Let's try this probably again.
I'm going to try this again. It's still
trying to this value gap. Yeah, it
stopped me out. It's not a problem at
all. Let's try this again.
So, I'm trying off order block over
here.
So exactly same approach. We got OB
entries open of next candle. I'm a bit
late. I'm going to put my stop loss at
swai and I'm going to aim for this uh 2
hour or liquidity level still wallet.
Here we go. Okay. Once again sometimes
yeah we can be a bit early but I I don't
believe like I was early. It just didn't
play out. It just was stop loss. It
happens. Um I entered again. So we got
one loss one win. Let's switch on
another day. All right, guys. Here's the
next day, March 21st. Uh, so it's 7:00
a.m. I'm going to ignore this uh
potential C because it's wrong time.
Let's switch on daily to see what bias
we have. So, we hit alltime high.
Amazing. This means we don't have levels
higher just yet like just new alltime
high on for chart.
So remember I'm not going to use for
chart as my P rate but I'm trying to use
for chart as
very reversal retracement. So so far yes
we're trying to expect for our volume
gap. Uh but I would like to enter long
only if it's going to break above 50% of
this week. So normally when we have huge
week and we highlighting 50% it's a
resistant and support levels. So this
means once everything is broken we will
go all the way up. Uh if it is trying to
stay below this level I'm still would
like to see slightly lower. So we have
volume and balance on for chart for the
tracement down and also we have
potential for our sweep. So still price
trying to stay below 50%.
Honestly, I would like to see price
going um to these lows at least, but
preferable to um fill this volume
balance. Okay. All right. Uh also, we
have news at 8:30 a.m.
So, this means we have news at 8:30 a.m.
I'm not going to try to trade before
8:30 a.m. I'm going to wait for a news
to first. Uh okay.
On hourly we are not expecting any
levels just yet. We have for a value gap
slightly. I mean we didn't fill this for
a value gap which by the way validates
idea to continue going lower to fill
like this part because as you can see we
filled half of this for a value gap. We
still have room to go lower.
All right. I would like to look for
short at least back to 92 95 area if
it's going to stay below this level
after news
comes out. Okay, going to see on three
minute chart. Here's 8:30 a.m.
over here. So, I'm going to wait for
news to came out first and I will try to
frame the trade right after this. Just
going to ignore everything here like
it's consolidation. See guys, we're
inside consolidation right now which is
typical when we have news at 8:30 a.m.
price trying to be inside consolidation.
But if with news price is going to break
this level 50% of our week I will look
for long otherwise not going to touch
this close to news. So guys we close to
news right now and we feel like we are
more bullish. I'm not going to touch
this. Uh but that's interesting just
interesting to see if it's going to uh
respect this order block. We just got
the closure like I'm going to just
highlight the setup but I'm not going to
take it because I'm going to wait for
news first
like for 2 hour just for now 2 hour stop
loss above swing high over here. Um
yeah target is 2 hour
guys news came out amazing. So what we
want to do so let's say we miss a trade.
Remember I talked about this like looks
like it wants to go in our favor because
interesting displacement but we are not
going to touch any order blocks within
this candle range. So this candle just
opened. We will see if it's going to
offer new order block within this candle
range. If so I will try the short
otherwise not going to touch this.
Did not hit just yet. Going higher
higher higher. Uh as you can see still
respecting this.
So I will try short if it's going to
close below this level. Um as
continuation once again
stop loss is going to be swing high and
I'm going to aim for 2 hour. As you can
see 2 R is way lower but it's right at
the sell side that you were watching
before. Okay, let's see. No rush. No
rush. Okay, here we go. Entry open of
next candle. This means it's going to be
even lower. I'm going to follow these
rules once again.
2 R is over here, right? As you can see,
uh this value gap and liquidity level.
I'm going to put my stop loss at swing
high, new swing high, and I'm going to
for 2 R. All right, let's see.
Okay, first like initial hour trade that
you were trying to forward test play
out. So I'm in this trade right now to
see if it's going to give me some money.
Also I have like the most important
question where I need to move at break
even. So normally I try to move at break
even once I'm up 1.5 R. So for example
I'm up 1.5 R. I would say it's okay to
trail stop loss to break even right now.
Hit. So we got continue pretty pretty
nice trade. Uh but honestly I felt like
it was risky to enter here because it
was right at news. So it did not make
any sense to trade right before news.
But I got continuation and I got UR okay
let's see next day. Well guys here's the
next trade uh next day Friday March
22nd. So we consolidated. Let's check
news.
We don't have any news at today. This
means we can trade before uh 8:30 a.m.
So let's see if it's going to be the
opportunity for us to trade before 8:20
a.m. So for now just consolidation. Look
at this gap. Seems like we got new
contract. Oh my god. Okay, we still
staying below this level. Um we fill
this gap I believe. Once again new
contract
we have here like right now it's
consolidation really nothing like to
consider for trade a flat candle on 30
minute chart which is still like okay I
might actually look for long 30 minute
flat candle so basically candle does not
have weak but if it's going to sweep
this so I expect to get the action
retracement back to this premium again
so we have untapped for a volume gap on
30 minute chart. So I might actually
look for like long
somewhere here to 50%.
But for now like I don't see a lot right
now to trade. I just don't see levels
that you can just expect right now like
on the 30 minute flat candle. See this
guys pretty much consolidation. So break
below consolidation. Yeah let's break
below consolidation. Let's take flat
candle then let's try to pump this.
Otherwise nothing for us. Okay guys
let's see. Let me delete this
for now. Yeah, pretty much lots of
weather things.
Oh, all right. I mean, maybe not only
flat candle, but I will consider this
low as well only because we have low
resistance here to downside. I may
actually consider long if it's going to
take this low and this low. So basically
we have failure swings, we have low
resistance to downside. I might actually
try to learn from that area if it's
going to take this. If not, then not. So
far, we don't have any potential sweeps.
We have nothing. It's 7:30 a.m. Still
nothing. Still nothing. Still not. Okay,
we took this.
All right,
we don't have any sweep here. Let's
switch. Let's just try to trade maybe
hourly. I know we didn't check this
before yet. Oh, okay. We do have it.
And five. Okay.
This was confirmed. That seems it's not
confirmed yet, by the way.
I may actually try to trade this, but
kind of don't like stop lossless.
Pretty. Oh, it's not big. Never mind.
It's just two points
for 2 hour. Once again, back to this
area. Just consolidation. 50% of this
consolidation. Nothing else. Like it's
five points. I'm not going to aim for
more if it's going to present this
opportunity. Okay. I'm going to try this
long. Uh I'm going to put entry here at
open of next candle. Stop loss below
this low. I'm going to enter for two
over here. Okay. Stop loss.
Okay. Target.
Yeah, pretty much accumulation
manipulation distribution. We filled gap
that we got over here.
So, back to this consolidation. I don't
I don't expect more than this. Let's see
how it goes. Maybe it's going to stop me
out. Who actually knows?
Which is fine as well.
All right. It filled my level but
honestly interesting to see if we may
get continuation here to this for a
value gap minor retracement but I feel
like it it may offer like this
opportunity
like 1.9R let's see just interesting how
it goes.
All right. It could play out as well.
Nothing interesting here. I I hate to
try to trade uh in deep premium. So, for
example, this range to aim for just
couple of points. It does not make does
not make any sense. But yeah, nice trade
over here as well. Okay, another vin
trade. Let's switch on next week because
it's Friday. So let's see how next week
is going to play out. Well guys, here's
Monday. So look at this reaction from
tournament free gap all the way down to
tournament flat candle. All right, looks
good. Looks good. Um let's see what we
have here.
We have we have untapped for a volume
gap. So we never touch this for a volume
gap. I might actually look for move over
there. But at least nothing respecting
right now. We have immediate rebalances
on uh here on hourly chart we expecting
nothing maybe on 15inut chart. Oh yeah
we have on 15inut chart for a value gap.
So let's see if price going to retrace
to this for a volume gap. So consider
something like this or something like
this.
Who is going to be fewest? We're going
to find out. Uh all right let's back on
diamond chart.
Once again we need to trade to height
from level. We are not going to trade in
from the nowhere right. Okay let's see.
Okay we hit this for a volume gap. We
hit this area for a volume gap on top
for a volume gap. This means we need to
confirm this reaction from uh using to
potential SE or SE. Let's see if it's
going to be confirmed by potential SE
first. We don't have sweep yet.
We don't have sweep yet. We don't have
sweep yet. We still don't have sweep.
Just going higher, higher, higher,
higher. We have potential sweep. Must be
confirmed by order block. This means we
need to close below sequence of uh up
close candles. We can short to this for
a value gap otherwise not touching this.
Let's see. Did not close yet.
Did not close yet. Did not close yet.
Keep going higher.
It's already 9:45.
No set up. I mean, we still have
something.
All right.
It's not sweep.
So, it must be of previous candle. By
the way, we got order block over here. I
just noticed this.
So, okay. I just noticed we got order
block over here after we got potential
sweep. So let's see if it's going to
play out. Just I miss this but I can try
right now because sorry guys I miss this
initially. Didn't realize this. Uh going
to try this. Let's see how it goes. So
back to this price action. Initially it
was potential SE and this was confirmed
by uh order block. So I need to try this
because it's according to our rules. We
hit our F value gap. We have untapped 15
minute volume gap lower. I mean we need
to try this otherwise
we are not going to find out.
All right. So my in pretty much where I
had to enter before. So I like it.
But for example right now yeah we can
see like it it wasn't sweep but in real
time it was potential sweep. So it's
already 11. It's already wrong time. But
since I'm in trade I'm just going to see
how it goes. Just interesting you know
guys.
See guys, I don't like to trade PM
session, it's already consolidation, so
nothing is going on. But even if it's
like stop loss, I'm going to just see
just interesting.
Oh my god, it's so slow. It's 3 p.m. and
nothing is going on.
So we know our target. Let's see where
is 1.5R because once we hit 1.5R, I can
move on break even. So it's not even
1.5R yet. Maybe it will, maybe not. It's
not going to be um anything here.
Yeah. All right.
It took forever. Just literally forever.
Look at this. Never hit it. But guys, we
traded to this for a while gap. I can
close the trade. But let's see. It's not
too R. Just interesting if it's going to
hit 2 R. If not, then perfect because we
were aiming for 15 volume gap.
I'm going to make this faster because
it's impossible to watch this.
Yeah, here's a break even. But once
again, we hit 15 minutes for a while. If
you could close this trade, it's already
a play out. So amazing. So perfect
trade. Anyway, well guys, here's a
Tuesday, March 26. We got like solid
reversal from this 15 minute bowl, which
I do like honestly. Let's see if we have
any news.
We do have news at 8:30 a.m. and going
to touch I'm not going to touch before
this. So, here's a 8:30 a.m. Uh, as you
can see, we broke about 50% of 4hour
week, but no entry for long at all.
Like, yeah, we broke above 50% of our
week. As I said before, we want to be
bullish, but as you can see, nothing
confirms the entry yet. Like, I'm not
going to blindly enter the trade simply
because I want to see something. Nope.
Let's see. Oh, by the way, let me bring
this back.
Okay,
just consolidation. We are not touching
before 8:2 a.m. We have news.
News came out. Okay, we got like really
nothing yet.
Price trying. Okay, guys. See, we have
potential sweep. Yes, we want to see
higher since price broke above 50% of
our week. This means we will look for
long if price is going to close above
this level. Otherwise, not touching
this.
We never closed. continue going lower.
See guys, that's why it's important to
wait
10:00 a.m. Still nothing.
So as you can see, we got internal
sweep. This means we did not hit any
height from level. We got internal sweep
which validate a slow probability. So
yeah, I do like we got sweep, but I
don't like that it was from nowhere. So
basically we didn't hit any level.
No reason to try to try this. We didn't
hit anything.
It's not speed yet. Still going. It's
12. Nothing. So this day we got nothing.
Next day. Well guys, let's actually try
to take not only premarket trades but
Asia session because it works exactly
the same way. Uh so here is 700 p.m. So
let's see if we got any trades before
during uh Asia session. So I believe we
got some sort of trade here. Um yeah, we
got some opportunities but let's book
this Asia as well because um it also
offers brilliant opportunities.
Uh all right let's see what we have for
now.
All right. All right. Consolidation. We
need to break above consolidation high
at least. You know like during Asia
don't expect to get big moves. So I mean
like we just waiting like huge levels
like 15 for a value gap like we need to
pump 12 points. No, not really. Let's
see if we got consolidation if it's
going to break above this consolidation
high and we will or consolidation low
and we will try to trade
inside consolidation still inside
consolidation. Okay. So basically
consolidation range is here just going
to highlight for you not only high but
low as well. We just broke above
consolidation high.
Here's guys what we got. We got
potential seas break above consolidation
high. Once again, exactly same approach.
Let's try to short this from the open of
next candle. Yeah, it's going to be like
not big move. Sometimes it's going to be
a couple of points, but still idea is to
aim for two R.
Let's try to short this. We can try it
with bigger size if you want. But idea
will remain the same. Exactly same
approach as we trade this um in session
or pre-market. Let's see how it goes.
Quick trade. Uh okay, let's try
premarket
Wednesday, March 27. Well, guys, here's
the next day. Let's see what we have. 7
a.m.
Let's see. Okay, we trace back to um
premium, right? We have 15 minute order
block. Pretty favorable to trade to this
order block. Let's see if it's so guys.
Let's see if it's going to trade to this
OB. Seems like not yet. 15 minute order
block. Okay. All right. Let's see what
else we have here. Let me delete old
level
from here. We have unbalanced part of
this fair value gap over here. Let me
extend this
like small for value gap. Extend this.
Right. Um yeah from premium like as you
can see we got reversal tracing to
premium from uh from discount to premium
discount premium let's see if we get
reaction down because we got untapped
for a value gap lower it's on 15 minute
chart let's see what else we have
yeah I will look for the drop to this
area per volume gap because pretty much
balanced move over here like nothing's
there yet. Yes, I'm going to look for
the auction. But first, let's let's see
if it's going to trade to these levels.
At least one of these levels. 15 OB or
unbalanced. Yeah, perfect. No questions
anymore. Let's see if it's going to be
potential sweep. Yeah, we do have
potential sweep. I already like it. I
may actually try this with bigger size
if you're going to present opportunity
for me. No sweep not confirmed yet. Ah,
okay.
Let's consider this as high probability.
All right, we got potential sweep. I may
actually try with two contracts because
when I'm extremely confident, I trade
with bigger size. So, I do like this.
I do like actually short small at small
uh stop loss like this.
I will try this two contracts. Let's
see. Wish me good luck everyone. Let's
see how it goes.
Uh I don't see brackets yet.
Okay, I don't see brackets for some
reason.
TP heat. I don't see brackets. Maybe
something went wrong. Let's me try to
buy this.
Yeah, close the trade. Well, guys,
here's the Asia. Same day. Let's see
what we have here. We don't really have
consolidation yet.
We we still sping the statement for
value gap untapped for value gap.
This means still valid P. Okay. Right
now nothing really is going on yet.
Uhhuh. We got the trap to this value. I
still can validate this by the way as
higher from level. Can we get potential
sweep? If so, I can actually try this
long
back to premium here.
see because we expecting same P. We can
dispect this several times. It's not a
problem at all.
Uhhuh. We got internal sweep.
I mean, okay, I cannot probably I can
trade micros here. Let's see. I can just
trade a couple of micros if I want.
Yeah, let's try this three micros here.
It's just low probability in my opinion
simply because we got internal S but we
just expecting 15 not fair value gap.
That's great.
Three micros
acceptable with small disc.
Yeah, when you're not confident, you
just can trade with small size. Micros
perfect.
Here we go. Play out. But once again,
with micros perfect with me, I would
feel probably stress. Okay, next day.
Let's try next day. Well, guys, here's
the first day, March 28.
We don't have any We do have news. My
bad. We have news at 8:30 a.m. Not
touching this. Before 8:30 a.m. and
let's see if it's going to offer
something right after this. Just going
to ignore price action before 8:30 a.m.
Uh, it's 8:30 a.m.
Well, perfect.
Let's see if it is fixing any levels on
15inut chart. Nothing yet. On hourly
chart. Yes. Hourly for a volume gap.
We expect an hourly for a volume gap. We
got reaction uh this with double sweep
three OB confirming this just one minute
contract.
Yeah.
So once again we tra pretty much bullish
market oral we just trace to our value
gap and we have like lower time frame.
Let me delete this for now. Lower time
frame demand OB here. Anyway, I'm going
to see like to collect more data how
it's going to be respected, but
preferably to close above this level,
but it's valid as well.
So, I'm up 1.5R, I believe. Let me see.
Not yet. Okay, 1.5 R is going to be
here.
Yeah, it's time to move at break even.
Um, we got quick move. Yeah, I'm just,
you know, I guess we got like straight
move up. I'm going to move at break
even. Let's see. It's 1.5 R. Yeah, just
going to move slightly in profit. We
never hit 2 R. It was so close. Ah,
really? It's okay. We got 1.9R.
Brilliant trade. Well, guys, here's the
Asia kill zone. We got gap here.
Partially fill this gap. Um, yeah, let's
see what will happen next. So we
partially fill this gap. We just got
potential sweep from this gap which is
valid as P. But I'm going to 15 minute
chart anyway. It's gap everywhere. So we
don't have any other P rays. So this
means I'm going to wait for the once
again. See this example. This candle low
is higher than this low. But I must I
must use this. Let's see if it's going
to close above this level. It's
extremely low dis like two points.
Not yet. Okay.
We just close. Let's try this long. So,
we partially filled gap. It's Asia. Uh,
we broke below consolidation low over
here. It offered potential sweep. Let's
see. It's like
two points risk. Probably
2.5. Yeah, it worth to try to make five
points. Five points during Asia session.
That's all you need, guys. Let's see.
Looking good. Here we are. Looks so
good. Looks so good.
Okay, it was Sunday. Let's do one more
day and I will I think it will be enough
because it's going to be long video if
I'm going to um continue trading like
another 10 15 trades. Yeah, let's do one
more day uh pre-market and probably Asia
and you you got the point how you need
to do this, how you need to book test
this. So high to frame bias, higher
frame level um reaction must be
confirmed by sweep uh on our 30 minute
chart and we executed on lower time
frame. Okay guys, let's switch on um
Monday, April 1st. Well guys, it's it's
Monday, April 1st, 7 a.m. Let's see what
levels we have.
Okay, we are inside our free value gap
for free value gap. We closed inside
this fair value gap. Probably if it's
going to trade inside this volume, I
will look for long back to this area. So
basically back to premium because I see
nothing else on hourly. Maybe 30 minute
chart will tell us more. Yeah, we have
end up for value gap lower slightly
lower and order block. So guys, I feel
like I will look for long anyway. Uh
it's 30 minute OB
just either from this level or from this
level it's nothing for me I don't really
see shorts opportunities once again.
Yeah
I will look for long to aim for like
trade from free volume gap to free
volume gap
from free volume gap to free volume gap.
Yeah let's see it's only seven. Okay
guys let's see if it's going to offer
potential sweep. It's okay. Let me
change the color like like this.
I would say uh I prefer to get
I'm wondering right now because I don't
I don't want to short just yet. I can
only look for long from this area or
from this area. But we don't have
potential sweep just yet. Okay.
Keep dropping.
Nothing yet. We do have potential sweep.
Let's see if we closed.
We didn't close. Well,
we just closed. Um, so let's actually
try this because we're still inside our
fair value gap.
The only issue probably 2 hours is going
to be way higher, but I'm actually just
cut the trade at this fair value if it's
going to go in my favor. How many
points? Okay, five points.
Here's a stop loss. Here's probably I
will trade maybe at break even if it's
going to go in my favor. Uh once again,
I feel like we uh retrace back to
discount untapped for value gap. Um
here's hourly for volume gap. We're
trying to respect this. Uh we have
untapped for volume gap on 15 higher. So
I believe this trade maybe slightly
against the height from trend overall
like we trying to retrace but okay if I
want to zoom out it's extremely bullish
so
I feel like it's can be a trade maybe
not a plus but like a trade
okay guys we just we just touch this I'm
not going to trail stop loss oh we
traded into Okay, let's trail. Okay,
that looks good.
I'm going to just probably trail my stop
loss. Looks so good to swing high, swing
low. Depends on the direction. Okay,
swing low here.
Okay, didn't hit 2 R but 15 minute for a
volume gap on top for a volume gap.
Amazing. Brilliant. Perfect. Okay, guys,
let's switch uh to Asia session and it's
going to be last trade in this back test
session for us. Here is the Asia 7 p.m.
Let's see what we have here. We got once
again overall bullish bias. We got to
trace them back to this fair value gap.
Well,
huge for but also you know like untapped
for a value gap, right? So what do you
mean by untapped? So basically for a
value gap that never was touched before,
right? So here's we traded into this for
a value gap. We got reversal. So Asia
probably is going to be uh bullish
simply because we have highs here. So we
didn't take any levels inside. Yeah, you
know like we size this for a volume gap
right now over here. Let's see if it
offered any reaction. Yeah, we got Marin
retracement down to another untapped for
a volume gap here. So yeah, I believe
just for now by side is TP for us.
This means we need to get long somehow
somehow. I mean we need to get potential
SIP on hour or 30 minute chart. As you
can see I kind of stuck at 30 minute
chart simply because it offers better
entry with better stop loss. Five minute
chart usually offers bigger stop loss.
Anyway, we need to get potential s
first.
Uhhuh. Let's see if it's going to
potential sip. It's not. It is. Okay.
I'm going to try probably long if it's
going to close above this level. Maybe
not for two hour.
Let's try this. Let's see how it goes
here. Okay. We discing like three points
to make six. Worth it. Worth it. Three
points is not really like big deal.
So once again, I'm aiming for sell side
by side over here. So that's it. That's
all I like. And stopped out. Anyway, I
still consider this as hyperb trade. I
do like this trade. Um not going to
touch this anymore. Didn't play out. We
took a loss. This happens but idea was
there. We just expected 15 minute on top
for a value gap. We retrace here. Uh
yeah, we got by side liquidity here. So
I did this as a A+ anyway. Just didn't
play out. Well guys, we took I guess 13
more trades or so. uh our win rate is a
bit higher but once again more trades we
taken less it's going to be so you don't
need to um say like oh it's 80% win rate
strategy with only 26 trades it means it
means nothing guys you need to get at
least three six months data to say yeah
it's 80% win rate strategy it's not
really yet so uh I will continue back
testing this to share the results
because once again 36 trades means
really nothing but I show you the point
how you want to back test this, how you
want to use higher trend, higher frame
levels to validate your setup. And I
hope guys you enjoy this. Don't forget
to subscribe to my YouTube channel if
you want to see more videos like this.
Let me know in the comments if you like
this kind of format like back test
sessions. And if you like this, I'm
going to do more this kind of back test
session specifically for this model.
Thank you guys so much for watching and
we'll see you next time. Bye-bye.